Harold Stein Filk Collection
Harold Stein Filk Archive
- Conventions
  - FilKONtario
    - FilKONtario 5, 31 Mar 1995 to 02 Apr 1995
      - Fk5 Main Concert, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: FilKONtario 5; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #23 (GG))
      - Fk5 Sat. mile main filk, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: FilKONtario 5; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #23 (GG))
      - Fk5 mini-concerts, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: FilKONtario 5; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #23 (GG))
    - FilKONtario 7, 11 Apr 1997 to 13 Apr 1997
    - FilKONtario 8, 17 Apr 1998 to 19 Apr 1998
      - Where the Magic is Real, 1999; Notes: USB-001 Origin: Convention: FilKONtario 8: 1998; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #23 (GG))
        Convention--FilKONtario 8: 1998; Professional Cassette
    - FilKONtario 10, 31 Mar 2000 to 02 Apr 2000
      - Filking from C to C: FilKONtario 10 edition, Volume 3, #1, 1 April 2000; Notes: From the collection of Judith Hayman, color cover with paintings and astrolabe and excited baby on back. Origin: Warner-Lalonde, Peggi Convention: FilKONtario 10; Zine 1 copy; Warner-Lalonde, Peggi (Box Box #13 (K))
        Warner-Lalonde, Peggi; Warner-Lalonde, Peggi; Convention--FilKONtario 10; Zine
    - FilKONtario 12, 29 Mar 2002 to 31 Mar 2002
    - FilKONtario 15, 01 Apr 2005 to 03 Apr 2005
      - Dragon For Sale: Songs from FilKONtario 15, 2017; Notes: Origin: USB Studios Convention: FilKONtario 15: 2005; Premium CD 1 copy (Box Box #21 (D))
        Various; USB Studios; Convention--FilKONtario 15: 2005; Premium CD
    - FilKONtario 17, 23 Mar 2007 to 25 Mar 2007
      - FilKONtario 17 publicity flier, 2007; Notes: Blue double sided flier with all the faces of the N'Early Music Consort lineup Origin: FilKONtario 17, March 23-25, 2007 Convention: FilKONtario 17; Flier 1 copy; FilKONtario 17 (Box Box #10 (P))
        FilKONtario 17; FilKONtario 17, March 23-25, 2007; Convention--FilKONtario 17; Flier
    - FilKONtario 24, 25 Apr 2014 to 27 Apr 2014
      - FilKONtario 24, 2014, Notes: Blue cover. Harold's badge is tucked into the program book, unworn, as it was a supporting membership. Origin: April 25-27, 2014 Convention: FilKONtario 24; Program book 1 copy (Box Box #09 (N))
        FilKONtario 24, 2014; April 25-27, 2014; Convention--FilKONtario 24; Program book
    - FilKONtario 25, 16 Apr 2015 to 19 Apr 2015
      - A Short History of the Great Butter War - or The Answers Behind Your Questions of "What's the Deal with all this Butter?" Documenting the conflict's origin in spring 2015 to the present day, Notes: White cover, pamphlet Origin: Convention: FilKONtario 25; Pamphlet 1 copy; FKO 2015 (Box Box #09 (N))
        FKO 2015; Convention--FilKONtario 25; Pamphlet
      - FilKONtario 25 Pocket Program, 2015; Notes: Printout Origin: FilKONtario 25, 16-19 April, 2015 Convention: FilKONtario 25; Pocket program 1 copy; FilKONtario 25 (Box Box #09 (N))
        FilKONtario 25; FilKONtario 25, 16-19 April, 2015; Convention--FilKONtario 25; Pocket program
      - FilkONTario 25, 2015, Notes: Harold's badge Origin: FilkONTario 25, April 16-19, 2015 Convention: FilKONtario 25; Con badge 1 copy; FilkONTario 25, April 16-19, 2015 (Box Box #09 (N))
        FilkONTario 25, April 16-19, 2015; FilkONTario 25, April 16-19, 2015; Convention--FilKONtario 25; Con badge
      - Schedule for FilKONtario 25, 2015; Notes: Origin: Convention: FilKONtario 25; Pocket program 1 copy; FilKONtario 25 (Box Box #07 (R))
        FilKONtario 25; Convention--FilKONtario 25; Pocket program
      - FIKONtario 25, 2015; Notes: This is a double sided schedule with the programming for the convention, as well as hours for the use of various rooms. Origin: Convention: FilKONtario 25: 2015; Schedule grid 1 copy (Box Box #02 (FF))
        FIKONtario 25; NA; Convention--FilKONtario 25: 2015; Schedule grid
      - FilKONtario 25 Program booklet, 2015; Notes: Origin: FiKONtario Convention: FilKONtario 25: 2015; Program booklet 2 copy; FilKONtario 26, April 16-19, 2015 (Box Box #07 (R))
        FilKONtario 26, April 16-19, 2015; NA; FiKONtario; Convention--FilKONtario 25: 2015; Program booklet
    - FilKONtario 26, 08 Apr 2016 to 10 Apr 2016
      - FilKONtario Pocket Program - FilKONtario 26, April 8-10, 2016, Notes: One sheet, double sided Origin: FilKONtario 26, April 8-10, 2016 Convention: FilKONtario 26: 2016; Pocket program 2 copy; FilKONtario 26, April 8-10, 2016 (Box Box #09 (N))
        FilKONtario 26, April 8-10, 2016; FilKONtario 26, April 8-10, 2016; Convention--FilKONtario 26: 2016; Pocket program
      - FilkONtario 26 Penguin Song Contest Rules, 2016; Notes: White half-sheet with the rules for the songwriting contest, song must contain Penguin, Titanium, Synergy, Entropy, Infinity Origin: Convention: FilKONtario 26: 2016; Rules 1 copy; FilKONtario 26 (Box Box #09 (N))
        FilKONtario 26; Convention--FilKONtario 26: 2016; Rules
      - FilKONtario 26, 2016; Notes: Blue booklet Origin: FilKONtario 26 Convention: FilKONtario 26: 2016; Program booklet 1 copy; FilKONtario 26, April 8-10, 2016 (Box Box #07 (R))
        FilKONtario 26, April 8-10, 2016; NA; FilKONtario 26; Convention--FilKONtario 26: 2016; Program booklet
    - FilKONtario 27, 21 Apr 2017 to 23 Apr 2017
      - FilkONtario 27 Penguin Song Contest Rules, 2017; Notes: White half-sheet with the rules for the songwriting contest, song must contain Penguin, Tartle, Abluvion, Bibliothecary, Collops Origin: FilKONtario 27 Convention: FilKONtario 27; Rules 1 copy; FilKONtario 27 (Box Box #09 (N))
        FilKONtario 27; FilKONtario 27; Convention--FilKONtario 27; Rules
      - FilKONtario 27, Pocket Program, 2017; Notes: One sheet, double sided. This is the schedule that infamously lists Daniel Gunderson (usually "Gundo") as "Guido". Origin: FilkONTario 27, April 21-23, 2017 Convention: FilKONtario 27: 2017; Pocket program 1 copy; FilkONTario 27, April 21-23, 2017 (Box Box #09 (N))
        FilkONTario 27, April 21-23, 2017; FilkONTario 27, April 21-23, 2017; Convention--FilKONtario 27: 2017; Pocket program
      - FilKONtario 27 Program Book, 2017; Notes: Blue cover Origin: FKO 27, April 21-23, 2017 Convention: FilKONtario 27: 2017; Program book 2 copy; FKO 27, April 21-23, 2017 (Box Box #09 (N))
        FKO 27, April 21-23, 2017; FKO 27, April 21-23, 2017; Convention--FilKONtario 27: 2017; Program book
      - Filk Hall of Fame Concert, FKO 27, 2017; Notes: One sheet, single sided Origin: FilkONTario 27, April 21-23, 2017 Convention: FilKONtario 27: 2017; List of Performers 1 copy; FilkONTario 27, April 21-23, 2017 (Box Box #09 (N))
        FilkONTario 27, April 21-23, 2017; FilkONTario 27, April 21-23, 2017; Convention--FilKONtario 27: 2017; List of Performers
      - Mike Whitaker's notes and lyrics and chords and sheet music from FKO set, 2017, Notes: Many sheets Origin: Convention: FilKONtario 27: 2017; Songs from set 1 copy (Box Box #09 (N))
        Convention--FilKONtario 27: 2017; Songs from set
      - Shawna Jacques Setlist from FKO 2017 Interfilk concert, Notes: Songs include: Mister Fox's Garden, QA Engineer Shanty, Dryads ... Harmless?, A Nation Called Panem, Battle of Serenity, Rains of Castamere, Fox Woman, The Grand Finale of Mister Fox, Rose Marshall's Ride, The Girl Who Couldn't Even Origin: Convention: FilKONtario 27: 2017; Set list 1 copy (Box Box #09 (N))
        Convention--FilKONtario 27: 2017; Set list
    - FilKONtario 28, 20 Apr 2018 to 22 Apr 2018
  - FuMPFest
    - FuMPFest 2014, 20 Jun 2014 to 22 Jun 2014
      Atlanda, GA
      - FuMPFest 2014, Notes: Includes a video of "We Are the FuMP" from closing ceremonies at FuMPFest 2014 Origin: The FuMP Convention: FuMPFest 2014; Commercial CD 1 copy; The FuMP (Box Box #05 (J))
        The FuMP; FuMP, The; The FuMP; Convention--FuMPFest 2014; Commercial CD
  - GAFilk
    - GAFilk 5, 10 Jan 2003 to 12 Jan 2003
      - GAFilk 2003 - Disc 2 01/11/03, Notes: Mini - 009 ninth box of minidiscs #3 Origin: Convention: GAFilk 5: 2003; MiniDisc 1 copy (Box Box #17 (AA))
        Convention--GAFilk 5: 2003; MiniDisc
      - GK-3 GAFilk 2003 Disc 3 01/11/03, Notes: Mini - 009 ninth box of minidiscs #4 Origin: Convention: GAFilk 5: 2003; MiniDisc 1 copy (Box Box #17 (AA))
      - GK-4 GAFilk 2003 Disc 4 01/11/03, Notes: Mini - 009 ninth box of minidiscs #5 Origin: Convention: GAFilk 5: 2003; MiniDisc 1 copy (Box Box #17 (AA))
    - GAFilk 7, 07 Jan 2005 to 09 Jan 2005
      - GAFilk 2005 - Banquet - disc 4, Notes: Mini - 007 seventh box of minidiscs #4 Origin: Convention: GAFilk 7: 2005; MiniDisc 1 copy (Box Box #17 (AA))
        Convention--GAFilk 7: 2005; MiniDisc
      - GAFilk 2005 - disc 1, Notes: Mini - 007 seventh box of minidiscs #1 Origin: Convention: GAFilk 7: 2005; MiniDisc 1 copy (Box Box #17 (AA))
      - GAFilk 2005 - disc 2, Notes: Mini - 007 seventh box of minidiscs #2 Origin: Convention: GAFilk 7: 2005; MiniDisc 1 copy (Box Box #17 (AA))
      - GAFilk 2005 - disc 3, Notes: Mini - 007 seventh box of minidiscs #3 Origin: Convention: GAFilk 7: 2005; MiniDisc 1 copy (Box Box #17 (AA))
      - GAFilk 2005 - disc 5, Notes: Mini - 007 seventh box of minidiscs #5 Origin: Convention: GAFilk 7: 2005; MiniDisc 1 copy (Box Box #17 (AA))
      - GAFilk 2005 - disc 6 - Eccumenifilk, Notes: Mini - 007 seventh box of minidiscs #6 Origin: Convention: GAFilk 7: 2005; MiniDisc 1 copy (Box Box #17 (AA))
    - GAFilk 8, 06 Jan 2006 to 08 Jan 2006
      - G6-1 GAFilk 2006 - disc 1, Notes: Mini - 014 fourteenth box of minidiscs #1 Origin: Convention: GAFilk 8: 2006; MiniDisc 1 copy (Box Box #17 (AA))
        Convention--GAFilk 8: 2006; MiniDisc
      - G6-2 GAFilk 2006 - disc 2, Notes: Mini - 014 fourteenth box of minidiscs #2 Origin: Convention: GAFilk 8: 2006; MiniDisc 1 copy (Box Box #17 (AA))
      - G6-3 GAFilk 2006 - disc 3, Notes: Loose in box Origin: Convention: GAFilk 8: 2006; MiniDisc 1 copy (Box Box #17 (AA))
      - G6-4 GAFilk 2006 - disc 4, Notes: Mini - 014 fourteenth box of minidiscs #3 Origin: Convention: GAFilk 8: 2006; MiniDisc 1 copy (Box Box #17 (AA))
      - G6-5 GAFilk 2006 - disc 5, Notes: Mini - 014 fourteenth box of minidiscs #4 Origin: Convention: GAFilk 8: 2006; MiniDisc 1 copy (Box Box #17 (AA))
      - G6-6 GAFilk 2006 - disc 6, Notes: Mini - 014 fourteenth box of minidiscs #5 Origin: Convention: GAFilk 8: 2006; MiniDisc 1 copy (Box Box #17 (AA))
      - G6-7 GAFilk 2006 - disc 7 Dandelion Wine - Stan Rogers Tribute Concert, Notes: Mini - 014 fourteenth box of minidiscs #6 Origin: Convention: GAFilk 8: 2006; MiniDisc 1 copy (Box Box #17 (AA))
        Dandelion Wine; Convention--GAFilk 8: 2006; MiniDisc
    - GAFilk 9, 05 Jan 2007 to 07 Jan 2007
      - G7-1 GAFilk 2007 - disc 1, 1 January 2007; Notes: Mini - 002 second box of minidiscs #1 Origin: Convention: GAFilk 9: 2007; MiniDisc 1 copy (Box Box #17 (AA))
        Convention--GAFilk 9: 2007; MiniDisc
      - G7-2 GAFilk 2007 - disc 2, 1 January 2007; Notes: Mini - 002 second box of minidiscs #2 Origin: Convention: GAFilk 9: 2007; MiniDisc 1 copy (Box Box #17 (AA))
      - G7-3 GAFilk 2007 - disc 3, 1 January 2007; Notes: Mini - 002 second box of minidiscs #3 Origin: Convention: GAFilk 9: 2007; MiniDisc 1 copy (Box Box #17 (AA))
      - G7-4 GAFilk 2007 - disc 4, 1 January 2007; Notes: Mini - 002 second box of minidiscs #4 Origin: Convention: GAFilk 9: 2007; MiniDisc 1 copy (Box Box #17 (AA))
      - G7-5 GAFilk 2007 - disc 5, 1 January 2007; Notes: Mini - 002 second box of minidiscs #5 Origin: Convention: GAFilk 9: 2007; MiniDisc 1 copy (Box Box #17 (AA))
    - GAFilk 10, 11 Jan 2008 to 13 Jan 2008
      - GAFilk program book, 2008; Notes: Yellow, pamphlet format, staple bound Origin: Convention: GAFilk 10: 2008; Program book 3 copy (Box Box #16 (Z))
        Convention--GAFilk 10: 2008; Program book
      - Gafilk 2008 2 AVI, Notes: Origin: Convention: GAFilk 10: 2008; Burnt CD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
        Convention--GAFilk 10: 2008; Burnt CD
      - GaFilk 2008, Disc 1, Notes: Origin: Floating Filk Studios Convention: GAFilk 10: 2008; Burnt CD 1 copy; GaFilk 2008; Floating Filk Studios (Box Somewhere safe (Possibly Box CC))
        GaFilk 2008; Floating Filk Studios; Various; Floating Filk Studios; Convention--GAFilk 10: 2008; Burnt CD
      - GaFilk 2008, Disc 2, Notes: This was Greg McMullen's last con, and there is photo and video footage of him from the My Filk game show Origin: Floating Filk Studios Convention: GAFilk 10: 2008; Burnt CD 1 copy; GaFilk 2008; Floating Filk Studios (Box Somewhere safe (Possibly Box CC))
      - GaFilk 2008 Sat Night, Dead Dog, Notes: Contains truncated files due (we think) to the file writing system Harold was using having a 2 GB limit. The files are still readable to that point, thank Ghu. Origin: Floating Filk Studios Convention: GAFilk 10: 2008; Burnt CD 1 copy; GAFilk 2008; Floating Filk Studios (Box Somewhere safe (Possibly Box CC))
        GAFilk 2008; Floating Filk Studios; Various; Floating Filk Studios; Convention--GAFilk 10: 2008; Burnt CD
      - GAFilk 10 Songbook, 2008; Notes: Blue cover with catfish in cowboy hat and musical notes. Spiral bound Origin: Convention: GAFilk 10: 2008; Songbook 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
        various; Convention--GAFilk 10: 2008; Songbook
      - GAFilk 10 Songbook, 2008; Notes: Blue cover with catfish in cowboy hat and musical notes. Spiral bound Origin: Convention: GAFilk 10: 2008; Songbook 1 copy (Box Box #16 (Z))
      - GAFilk Songbook, 2008; Notes: Blue cover, spiral bound Origin: Convention: GAFilk 10: 2008; Songbook 1 copy (Box Box #16 (Z))
    - GAFilk 11, 09 Jan 2009 to 11 Jan 2009
      - Emma Bull at GaFilk 2009, Notes: Origin: Produced for the Magick4Terri Auction Convention: GAFilk 11: 2009; Burnt CD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
        Produced for the Magick4Terri Auction; Convention--GAFilk 11: 2009; Burnt CD
      - GAFilk 11 Songbook, 2009; Notes: Purple cover with large 11. Spiral bound Origin: Convention: GAFilk 11: 2009; Songbook 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
        Convention--GAFilk 11: 2009; Songbook
      - GAFilk 11 Songbook, 2009; Notes: Purple cover with large 11. Spiral bound Origin: Convention: GAFilk 11: 2009; Songbook 1 copy (Box Box #16 (Z))
    - GAFilk 12, 08 Jan 2010 to 10 Jan 2010
      - GAFilk 12 Songbook, 2010; Notes: Light green cover with GAFilkafish on number 12 Origin: Convention: GAFilk 12: 2010; Songbook 3 copy (Box Box #16 (Z))
        various; Convention--GAFilk 12: 2010; Songbook
    - GAFilk 13, 07 Jan 2011 to 09 Jan 2011
      Atlanta, GA, USA
      - GAFilk 13 Songbook, 2011; Notes: Orange cover, with cat fishing in GAFilkafish bowl, spiral bound Origin: Convention: GAFilk 13: 2011; Songbook 2 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
        Convention--GAFilk 13: 2011; Songbook
      - GAFilk 13, program booklet, 2011; Notes: Yellow cover, staple bound Origin: Convention: GAFilk 13: 2011; Program book 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
        Convention--GAFilk 13: 2011; Program book
    - GAFilk 14, 06 Jan 2012 to 09 Jan 2012
      - GAFilk 2012 Pocket Program, Notes: Yellow cover, pamphlet style, staple bound Origin: Convention: GAFilk 14: 2012; Pocket program 1 copy (Box Box #16 (Z))
        Convention--GAFilk 14: 2012; Pocket program
      - Program book, GAFilk 2012, Notes: Goldenrod colored program book Origin: Convention: GAFilk 14: 2012; Program book 1 copy; GAFilk 2012 (Box Box #08 (O))
        GAFilk 2012; Convention--GAFilk 14: 2012; Program book
      - GAFilk 2012 Play It With Moxie setlist and liner notes (tucked into a pocket), Notes: Green cover with two CD pockets and a pocket in the back for liner notes. Possibly bought in an Interfilk Auction Origin: Convention: GAFilk 14: 2012; Two CD set with setlist 1 copy; Play It With Moxie (Box Box #08 (O))
        Play It With Moxie; Play It With Moxie; Convention--GAFilk 14: 2012; Two CD set with setlist
      - GAFilk 2012 Songbook, Notes: Blue cover with GAFilkafish Origin: Convention: GAFilk 14: 2012; Songbook 3 copy (Box Box #16 (Z))
        various; Convention--GAFilk 14: 2012; Songbook
    - GAFilk 15, 11 Jan 2013 to 13 Jan 2013
      - GAFilk 15 Songbook, 2013; Notes: Goldenrod cover, Spiral bound with GAFilkafish on a lucky horsehshoe. Limited edition, 6/8 Origin: Convention: GAFilk 15: 2013; Songbook 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
        Convention--GAFilk 15: 2013; Songbook
      - GAFilk 2013 Disc 1 Friday Concert and Bonus - Raw Video by James Folkerson, Notes: Origin: Convention: GAFilk 15: 2013; Burnt DVD 2 copy (Box Box #21 (D))
        Convention--GAFilk 15: 2013; Burnt DVD
      - GAFilk 2013 Disc 2 Additional Concerts - Raw Video by James Folkerson, Notes: Origin: Convention: GAFilk 15: 2013; Burnt DVD 2 copy (Box Box #21 (D))
    - GAFilk 16, 09 Jan 2014 to 11 Jan 2014
      - GAFilk 16, Sweet Sixteen Songbook, 2014; Notes: Pink cover, spiral bound, Limited print edition 2/20 Origin: Convention: GAFilk 16: 2014; Songbook 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
        Convention--GAFilk 16: 2014; Songbook
      - GAFilk 16, program booklet, 2014; Notes: Yellow cover, staple bound Origin: Convention: GAFilk 16: 2014; Program book 2 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
        Convention--GAFilk 16: 2014; Program book
      - GAFilk 2014, Soundboard copy, Notes: Yellow booklet, Someone has written Sound Board Copy Do Not Remove on the front Origin: GAFilk 2014 Convention: GAFilk 16: 2014; Program book 1 copy; GAFilk 2014 (Box Box #08 (O))
        GAFilk 2014; GAFilk 2014; Convention--GAFilk 16: 2014; Program book
      - Gafilk Songbook 2014, Notes: Limited edition run, 1/32 Green cover, spiral bound, winged GAFilka fish Origin: Convention: GAFilk 16: 2014; Songbook 1 copy; GAFilk 2014, January 9-11 (Box Box #08 (O))
        GAFilk 2014, January 9-11; Convention--GAFilk 16: 2014; Songbook
    - GAFilk 17, 09 Jan 2015 to 11 Jan 2015
      - GAFilk 2015, Notes: Yellow booklet Origin: GAFilk 2015, January 9-11 Convention: GAFilk 17: 2015; Program book 1 copy; GAFilk 2015, January 9-11 (Box Box #08 (O))
        GAFilk 2015, January 9-11; GAFilk 2015, January 9-11; Convention--GAFilk 17: 2015; Program book
      - GAFilk 2015 The Songbook (Limited Print Edition #16/32), Notes: Origin: Convention: GAFilk 17: 2015; Songbook copy (Box JW Blue suitcase)
        Convention--GAFilk 17: 2015; Songbook
      - GAFilk 2015, January 9-11, Notes: This is a yellow covered stapled booklet from 2015. The guests were GOH: S.J. Tucker, Toasmasters: The Blibbering Humdingers, Interfilk Guest: C.D. Woodbury, Super Secret Guest: Robin W. Baily, and featuring Play It With Moxie! ConCom's Choice concert: Marc Gunn Origin: Convention: GAFilk 17: 2015; Program booklet 1 copy; GAFilk; GAFilk 2015 (Box Box #02 (FF))
        GAFilk; GAFilk 2015; NA; Convention--GAFilk 17: 2015; Program booklet
    - GAFilk 18, 08 Jan 2016 to 10 Jan 2016
      - GAFilk 2016 Songbook, Notes: Red cover, spiral bound - Limited edition printing 30/45 Origin: GAFilk 2016, January 8-10, 2016 Convention: GAFilk 18: 2016; Songbook 1 copy; GAFilk 2016; GAFilk 2016, January 8-10, 2016 (Box Box #09 (N))
        GAFilk 2016; GAFilk 2016, January 8-10, 2016; GAFilk 2016, January 8-10, 2016; Convention--GAFilk 18: 2016; Songbook
      - GaFilk 2017 Fundraiser, Notes: Origin: Convention: GAFilk 18: 2016; Burnt CD 1 copy (Box Box #21 (D))
        Convention--GAFilk 18: 2016; Burnt CD
      - GAFilk, 8 January 2016; Notes: Orange booklet Origin: GAFilk Convention: GAFilk 18: 2016; Program booklet 1 copy; GAFilk, January 8-10, 2016 (Box Box #07 (R))
        GAFilk, January 8-10, 2016; GAFilk; NA; GAFilk; Convention--GAFilk 18: 2016; Program booklet
    - GAFilk 19, 06 Jan 2017 to 08 Jan 2017
      - GAFilk 2017 Pocket Program, Notes: Yellow cover, pocket program Origin: GaFilk 2018, January 6-8, 2017 Convention: GAFilk 19: 2017; Pocket program 1 copy; GaFilk 2018, January 6-8, 2017 (Box Box #09 (N))
        GaFilk 2018, January 6-8, 2017; GaFilk 2018, January 6-8, 2017; GaFilk 2018, January 6-8, 2017; Convention--GAFilk 19: 2017; Pocket program
      - GAFilk 2017, 6 January 2017; Notes: Yellow booklet Origin: Convention: GAFilk 19: 2017; Program booklet 3 copy; GAFilk, January 6-8, 2017 (Box Box #07 (R))
        GAFilk, January 6-8, 2017; NA; Convention--GAFilk 19: 2017; Program booklet
      - GAFilk 2017, Program book, Notes: Origin: GAFilk 2015, January 9-11 Convention: GAFilk 19: 2017; Program booklet 1 copy; GAFilk 2017; GAFilk 2015, January 9-11 (Box Box #07 (R))
        GAFilk 2017; GAFilk 2015, January 9-11; NA; GAFilk 2015, January 9-11; Convention--GAFilk 19: 2017; Program booklet
      - GAFilk setlist Leslie Hudson, 2017; Notes: Four handwritten pages. Set list: Double Trouble, Sister & Sinners, Call the Doctor, Leslie might be Leslie Hudson, For a While, Oars in the Water, Troublemaker, Black Belt, Feel It All, Vasilisa Trilogy, Any Wya the Wind Blows Origin: GAFilk 2017 Convention: GAFilk 19: 2017; Set list 1 copy; GAFilk 2017 (Box Box #07 (R))
        GAFilk 2017; Various; GAFilk 2017; Convention--GAFilk 19: 2017; Set list
      - GaFilk 2017 Songbook: Ye Olde Songbooke, Notes: Produced by Mary Crowell, Spiral bound Origin: January 6-8, 2017, limited print edition, 15/40 Convention: GAFilk 19: 2017; Songbook 1 copy; GAFilk 2017 (Box Box #07 (R))
        GAFilk 2017; Various; January 6-8, 2017, limited print edition, 15/40; Convention--GAFilk 19: 2017; Songbook
    - GaFilk 20, 05 Jan 2018 to 07 Jan 2018
      - GAFilk 2018 Pocket Program, Notes: Goldenrod cover, pocket program Origin: GaFilk 2018, January 5-7, 2018 Convention: GaFilk 20: 2018; Pocket program 1 copy; GaFilk 2018, January 5-7, 2018 (Box Box #09 (N))
        GaFilk 2018, January 5-7, 2018; GaFilk 2018, January 5-7, 2018; GaFilk 2018, January 5-7, 2018; Convention--GaFilk 20: 2018; Pocket program
      - GAFilk 2018 Songbook, Notes: Three piece green and white cover with Emerald, limited edition songbook 1/36 Origin: January 5-7, 2018 Convention: GaFilk 20: 2018; Songbook 1 copy; GAFilk 2018 (Box Box #09 (N))
        GAFilk 2018; January 5-7, 2018; Convention--GaFilk 20: 2018; Songbook
  - GAFIlk
    - GAFilk 6, 09 Jan 2004 to 11 Jan 2004
      - G4-7 GAFilk 2004 Banquet, Disc 7, Notes: Mini - 013 thirteenth box of minidiscs #5 Origin: Convention: GAFilk 6: 2004; MiniDisc 1 copy (Box Box #17 (AA))
        Convention--GAFilk 6: 2004; MiniDisc
  - Heliosphere
    - HELIOsphere 2018, 09 Mar 2018 to 11 Mar 2018
  - I-CON
    - I-CON 8, 31 Mar 1989 to 02 Apr 1989
    - I-CON 21, 19 Apr 2002 to 21 Apr 2002
      Stony Brook, NY
      - Frank Hayes at I-Con 2002 (Concert ?) Has some skips, tracks labelled at least some 41 tracks 98:26, Notes: Mini - 008 eighth box of minidiscs #11 Origin: Convention: I-CON 21: 2002; MiniDisc 1 copy (Box Box #17 (AA))
        Convention--I-CON 21: 2002; MiniDisc
      - I-Con 21-1 Fri. Sat. 4/19-20/02, Notes: Mini - 008 eighth box of minidiscs #8 Origin: Convention: I-CON 21: 2002; MiniDisc 1 copy (Box Box #17 (AA))
      - I-Con 21-2 Sat 4/20/02 Panels, Notes: Mini - 008 eighth box of minidiscs #12 Origin: Convention: I-CON 21: 2002; MiniDisc 1 copy (Box Box #17 (AA))
      - I-Con 21-4 Sat 4/20/02 Concert and Caberet, Notes: Mini - 008 eighth box of minidiscs #13 Origin: Convention: I-CON 21: 2002; MiniDisc 1 copy (Box Box #17 (AA))
    - I-CON 25, 24 Mar 2006 to 26 Mar 2006
      - I-CON 25 - Recordings, Notes: Origin: Convention: I-CON 25; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
        Convention--I-CON 25; Burnt DVD
      - I-CON 25 - Recordings - Garage Band Files - Mac Format - 4/05, 1 April 2005; Notes: Origin: Convention: I-CON 25; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - I-CON 27, 04 Apr 2008 to 06 Apr 2008
      Ronkonkoma/Islip, NY, USA
      - I-CON 27 Souvenir Program Guide, Notes: People with riding biped, on alien world. Staple bound Origin: Convention: I-CON 27: 2008; Program book 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
        Convention--I-CON 27: 2008; Program book